nutronix.com 2009-10-16

# Welcome to Nutronix International - Privacy Policy

**Copyright:  
**  
Nutronix ™ Incorporated. All Rights Reserved. This is an Official Nutronix Incorporated Web site. The materials on these Web pages are copyrighted by Nutronix Incorporated. Permission is given to view and/or print the material on this Web site and save the materials for your future personal reference but do not copy, modify, use, distribute or create any derivative works unless you obtain the express permission of Nutronix Incorporated. Express written permission must be received by Nutronix Incorporated for Web site owners who wish to link their site to Nutronix, except for Nutronix Independent Associates. Nutronix Incorporated is not able to inspect or confirm that the material contained on the Web sites that are linked to this site are correct in every case. Nutronix Incorporated does not authorize the material on any external Web site linked to this or any other official Nutronix Incorporated Web site. Nutronix Incorporated may make changes to materials, the product information and the prices at any time without notice and without obligation to update the materials on this Web site.

 **Terms of Use:**  
These Web sites are based in Mechanicsville, Virginia, U.S.A. The Company makes no claims that the information located herein is appropriate or may be downloaded legally outside of the United States, Canada, Australia, the United Kingdom or Japan. Access to the materials may not be legal by certain persons in certain countries. If you access this Web site from outside of the United States, Canada, Australia, the United Kingdom or Japan you do so at your own risk and are responsible for compliance with the laws in your respective jurisdiction. This site is governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of Virginia.

 **Gathering and Use of Information:**  
On most sections of our website, Nutronix collects personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis. We do not require this information for customers to obtain access to our site. However, visitors may have to provide certain personal information in order to participate in some of our programs offered on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used solely for internal marketing purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.

 **Cookies:**  
Nutronix may use "cookie" technology to obtain non-personal information from its online visitors. Cookies are information files that your web browser automatically places from your computer when you visit a website. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but can be configured not to accept them or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. We do not extract personal information in this process nor do we provide this information to third-parties. Cookies allow us to customize your user interface to speed up the navigation process and to make the site experience more meaningful, fun and efficient. If your browser is configured to reject cookies, you will not be able to utilize the features of our website.

 **Privacy Policy:**

Privacy Policy Coverage

  * This Privacy Policy covers Nutronix’s treatment of personally identifiable information that Nutronix collects when you are on a Nutronix site, and when you use Nutronix's services.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Nutronix does not own or control, or to people that Nutronix does not employ or manage.

Information Collection and Use

  * Nutronix collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Nutronix account, when you use certain Nutronix products or services, when you visit Nutronix pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes.
  * If you register to become a Nutronix Independent Associate or Member, we may ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, social security number and/or tax identification number. Once you register with Nutronix and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * Nutronix also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address,
  * Nutronix cookie information and the page you requested.
  * Nutronix uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * Nutronix will not sell, rent or exchange your personally identifiable information to anyone.
  * Nutronix may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
    * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Nutronix Terms of Service, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

Security

  * Your Nutronix Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.
  * In certain areas Nutronix uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * Nutronix may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

 **Forward-Looking Statements:**  
Some of the statements containing herein may constitute "forward-looking statements" within the meaning of Section 27A of the Securities Act of 1933 and Section 21E of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934 and are subject to certain events, risks and uncertainties that maybe outside of our control. These forward-looking statements include statements relating to the projected sales; actual sales including by country; number of Associates; future plans and earnings per share projections. In some cases, forward-looking statements are identified by terminology such as "may," "will," "should," "could," "expects," "plans," "intends," "anticipates," 'believes," "estimates," "approximates," "predicts," "potential" or "continue' or the negative of such terms and other comparable terminology.

Actual results, plans or developments could differ materially from those expressed in or implied by such statements herein due to a number of factors, including, without limitations; those described in the context of such forward-looking statements; the entrance into new countries and markets; the risk factors described from time to time in other documents and reports filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission.

Although we believe that the expectations reflected in our forward-looking statements are reasonable, we cannot guarantee future results, levels of activity, performance or achievements. Moreover, neither we nor anyone else assumes responsibility for the accuracy and completeness of such statements, and we are under no duty to update any of the forward-looking statements after the date this information is published.

Actual results, plans or developments could differ materially from those expressed in or implied by such statements herein due to a number of factors, including, without limitations; those described in the context of such forward-looking statements; the entrance into new countries and markets; the risk factors described from time to time in other documents and reports filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission.

Although we believe that the expectations reflected in our forward-looking statements are reasonable, we cannot guarantee future results, levels of activity, performance or achievements. Moreover, neither we nor anyone else assumes responsibility for the accuracy and completeness of such statements, and we are under no duty to update any of the forward-looking statements after the date this information is published.
